我不知道  什么
Hmm. Oh, I don't know. What?
照狗的年纪来算…
Well, as old as he is in dog years...
你觉得史努比可以驾驶飞机吗
...do you think Snoopy should still be allowed to fly this thing?
瑞秋  什么
Rachel? Yeah?
还记得你刚来的时候  另一位服务生训练你两星期吗
Remember when you came, you spent two weeks getting trained by another waitress?
当然  你要我训练新人吗
Oh, sure. Do you need me to train somebody new?
很好笑
Ha-ha-ha. Good one.
事实上泰利要你再受训一次
Actually, uh, Terry wants you to take the training again.
等你有空的时候
Whenever.
你相信吗
Do you believe that?
相信
Yeah.
《老友记》 第三季 第10集  瑞秋辞职
Friends S03E10  The One Where Rachel Quits
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
一共是两盒佳节杏仁饼干
So that's two boxes of the Holiday Macaroons.
我代表美国棕鸟(女童军团体)向您致敬
On behalf of the Brown Birds of America, I salute you.
承认吧  你的反手拍打不好
Just admit it. You have no backhand.
对不起  小家伙  我的反手拍打得非常好
Excuse me, little one. I have a very solid backhand.
你用手挡住脸  跟小女孩一样蹲下来
Shielding your face and shrieking like a girl...
那不算是反手拍
...is not a backhand.
我的确蹲了下来
I was shrieking...
跟海军陆战队一样
...like a Marine.
好吧  听我说  你得做到冠军3P原则
All right, here, watch me execute the three P's of championship play.
力量
Power, huah...
精准
...precision, shew...
架式
...and panache.
你害一个小女孩摔断腿
You broke a little girl's leg?
我知道  我很难过  好吗
I know. I feel horrible, okay?
报上说昨晚有个布偶  在芝麻街被打了
It says here that a Muppet got whacked on Sesame Street last night.
十点多时你在哪里
Where exactly were you around 10-ish?
我得去看她  买些东西送她
Well, I'm gonna go see her. I wanna bring her something.
你觉得她会喜欢什么   或许你该送她凯蒂猫娃娃
What do you think she'd like? Maybe a Hello Kitty doll?
行走能力
The ability to walk?
我得回去受训了
I'm gonna get back to retraining. Ahem.
好吧  大家再见
All right. See you guys.
小心点  孩子们  他来了
Look out, kids. He's coming.
我得去卖圣诞树
And I gotta go sell some Christmas trees.
祝你玩得开心  等一下  不  别那么做
Have fun. Oh, wait. No, don't.
我忘了  我百分之百反对那种事
I forgot. I am totally against that now.
什么   你反对我有工作
What? Me having a job?
不  我反对无辜的树  在青春正盛的时候被砍下…
No, no. I am against innocent trees being cut down in their prime...
华丽地装饰它们的尸体
...and their corpses grotesquely dressed...
挂上一堆金箔和闪灯
...in, like, tinsel and twinkly lights.
你晚上怎么睡得着呢
Hey, how do you sleep at night?
整天搬树可把我累坏了
Well, I'm pretty tired from lugging the trees around.
菲比  听我说
Hey, Phoebe, listen.
你误会了
You got this all wrong.
那些树生来要当圣诞树
Those trees were born to be Christmas trees.
它们完成了毕生志愿   让大家感到开心
They're fulfilling their life purpose by making people happy.
真的吗
Really?
对
Yes.
对  树也很开心
Yes, and, uh, the trees are happy too...
因为对多数的树来说  这是它们参观纽约的唯一机会
...because for most of them, it's their only chance to see New York.
上饮料后  你得拿着空托盘…
After you've delivered the drinks, you take the tray...
阿甘  拜托  我在这里工作了两年半
Gunther, Gunther, please. I have worked here for two and a half years.
我知道空托盘得放在那边
I know the empty trays go over there.
放在这里怎么样
What if you put them here?
知道吗  这倒是个好主意  离马克杯比较近
You know, that's actually a good idea. They'll be closer to the mugs.
你知道吗  你该要求其他服务生也那么做
You know what? You should have the other waitresses do that too.
他们早就那么做了
They already do. Huh?
所以他们叫这里是托盘区
That's why they call it "the tray spot."
我常听到他们那么说  我以为那是他们去玩的夜店
I always heard them talk about that. I just thought it was a club they went to.
喔  天啊
Oh, God.
对不起  没关系
I'm sorry.  It's all right.
甜心
Sweetheart.
你一定很高兴吧
So this must be kind of neat for you, huh?
你爸跟我说你得跟学校请假几天
Your dad tells me you get a couple of days off school...
也不必再去卖饼干了
...and you don't have to sell those cookies anymore.
我想去卖饼干
Well, I kind of wanted to sell the cookies.
卖最多饼干的女孩能参加太空营
The girl who sells the most wins a trip to Space Camp...
坐在真的太空梭里
...and gets to sit in a real space shuttle.
哇  看来你真的很喜欢太空对吗
Wow, you really like all this space stuff, huh?
对  我爸说只要我帮他清洁公寓的时间
Yeah. My dad says if I'd spend as much time helping him clean apartments...
和我做太空梦的时间一样多
...as I do daydreaming about outer space...
他就会赚到足够的钱  去秦姬陵玩
...he'd be able to afford a trip to the Taj Mahal.
我想你得打扫很多公寓  才能去印度玩
I think you'd have to clean a whole lot of apartments to go all the way to India.
不  是大西洋城那一个  爸爸喜欢玩吃角子老虎
No, the one in Atlantic City. Dad loves the slots.
他说他可以让奶奶  留给我的大学基金翻成两倍
He says he's gonna double the college money my grandma left me.
祝你爸好运
Well, good luck to Dad.
你还得卖几盒饼干才能赢
Say, how many more boxes would you have to sell in order to win?
去年的冠军卖了475盒  是吗
The girl who won last year sold 475. Yeah?
目前我卖了75盒
So far, I've sold 75.
还差四百盒
Four hundred, huh?
听起来不难  一盒多少钱
Well, that sounds doable. How much are the boxes?
五块钱
Five dollars a box.
第二名能拿到什么奖品
And what is second prize?
十段变速自行车
A 10-speed bike.
我想要爸爸卖不掉的奖品
But I'd rather have something my dad couldn't sell.
听起来很合理
Well, that makes sense.
你能帮我一个忙吗  希望不会太麻烦你
Could you do me one favor? If it's not too much trouble.
当然  莎拉  没问题  你能帮我拉窗帘吗
Yeah, Sarah, anything. Could you pull the curtains open for me?
太空梭的太空人一定会上新闻
The astronauts from the space shuttle are gonna be on the news.
因为我们家没有电视  对面巷子的女士说
Since we don't have a TV, the lady across the alley...
说她会把她的电视  推到窗口让我看
...said she'd push hers up to her window so I can watch it.
什么事
Yes?
你好  我来卖棕鸟饼干
Yeah, hi. I'm selling Brown Bird cookies.
你不是棕鸟女童军  我能从窥视孔看到你
You're no Brown Bird. I can see you through my peephole.
不  我是荣誉棕鸟女童军
Um, no, hi. I'm an honorary Brown Bird.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
那代表我可以卖饼干  但不能参加过夜派对
Uh, well, it means that I can sell cookies, but I'm not invited to sleepovers.
我一按按钮  就可以跟警局连线
I can dial 911 at the press of a button, you know.
快滚开
Now, go away.
拜托  这是为了一个可怜的贫穷小女孩
Please, please. It's for a poor little girl...
她真的很想去参加太空营
...who wants to go to Space Camp more than anything in the world.
我按下按钮了  不
I'm pressing. No...
警察马上就到
A policeman is on his way.
好吧   我走就是了
Okay, okay. I'm going, I'm going.
我还是看得到你  好啦
I can still see you. All right.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  你在这里干嘛
Hey. What are you doing here?
我一直在想你说的话
Well, I thought a lot about what you said...
我了解到或许我太爱批评了
...and I realized, all right, maybe I was a little judgmental.
对  可是…
Yeah. Oh, but, oh. Ugh.
好了  菲比  记住
Now, now, Phoebe, remember, hey...
它们只是在完成它们的圣诞节…
...they're just fulfilling their Christmas...
使命  对  没错
Destiny. Yes. Sure.
对  好吧
Right. Okay.
那一棵看起来无法完成使命
Yikes. That one doesn't look very fulfilled.
那是棵老树  他只是把它搬到后面
Oh, that's one of the old ones. He's just taking it to the back.
你们把老树搬到后面
You keep the old ones in the back?
那是年龄歧视
That is so ageist.
我们得挪出空间放新树   那老树怎么处理
We have to make room for the fresh ones. So, what happens to the old guys?
拿去切碎
Well, they go into the chipper.
我感觉好像不怎么快乐似的
Why do I have a feeling that's not as happy as it sounds?
不…
No. No!
嘿..
Hey, hey, hey.
中央咖啡厅
这些是圣诞节人物的造型
And these come in the shapes of Christmas characters.
圣诞老人  鲁道夫跟耶稣基督宝宝
Santa, Rudolph and Baby Jesus.
好吧  我要一盒奶油口味的耶稣基督
All right. I'll take a box of the cream-filled Jesuses.
等一下  一盒  我要送可怜小女孩到太空营
Wait a minute, one box? I'm trying to send a poor little girl to Space Camp.
我帮你登记五盒  钱德  你呢
I'm putting you down for five boxes. Chandler, what about you?
好吧  有椰子口味  天神造型饼干吗
All right, do you have any, uh, coconut-flavored deities?
没有  但是有椰子口味  光明节烛台造型饼干
No, but there's coconut in the Hanukkah Menorah-eos.
我帮你登记八盒  每晚一盒
I'll put you down for eight boxes, one for each night.
好吧
Okay.
摩妮卡   我要一盒薄荷宝藏
Mon?  I'll take one box of the Mint Treasures.
一盒  就那样
One, and that's it.
我加入棕鸟后体重开始增加
I started gaining weight after I joined the Brown Birds.
还记得爸买光了我的饼干  而我把它们都吃光了吗
Remember Dad bought every one of my boxes and I ate them all?
不  摩妮卡  爸必须买光你的饼干
No, Mon, Dad had to buy every one of your boxes...
因为你把它们吃光了
...because you ate them all.
但我相信这一次不会是那样的
But, you know, I'm sure that's not gonna happen this time.
我何不帮你登记三盒薄荷宝藏
Why don't I just put you down for three Mint Treasures...
两盒鲁道夫呢
...and just a couple of the Rudolphs?
不
No.
少来了  你知道你很想吃
Oh, come on, now. You know you want them.
别这么做
Don't do this.
听我说  摩妮卡  第一盒我免费送你
I'll tell you what, Mon. I'll give you the first box for free.
天啊  我得走了
Oh, God, I gotta go.
别这样  酷小孩都会吃的
Come on. All the cool kids are eating them.
等一下我要教你  为什么我们不能只拿马克杯
And later I wanna show you why we don't just trap spiders...
把蜘蛛困在里面后就不管了
...under coffee mugs and leave them there.
我痛恨这工作  还要努力改进  我的人生算是完了
I'm training to be better at a job that I hate. My life officially sucks.
这不是过渡期而已吗   我以为你要踏入时尚界
But wasn't this supposed to be temporary? I thought you wanted to do fashion stuff.
对  我还没有放弃啊
Well, yeah, I'm still pursuing that.
你是怎么不放弃的呢
How, exactly, are you pursuing that?
除了你在两年前寄出的履历表
You know, other than sending out resumes, like, what, two years ago?
我还是有很多…
Well, I'm also sending out...
好点子
...good thoughts.
我想只要你继续做这份工作
If you ask me, as long as you got this job...
你就不会想找其他工作
...you got nothing pushing you to get another one.
你需要恐惧
You need The Fear.
恐惧  他说的对
The Fear? He's right.
要是你辞掉这份工作   你就会有动力
If you quit this job, you then have motivation...
去找你想做的事
...to go after a job you really want.
为什么你还在做你讨厌的工作   干嘛不辞职  来产生恐惧
How come you're still at a job you hate? Why don't you quit and get The Fear?
因为我太害怕了
Because I'm too afraid.
天啊  我不知道
God. I don't know.
我愿意付出一切为设计师工作或采购
I mean, I would give anything to work for a designer, you know, or a buyer.
我不想到了三十岁  还在这里工作
Ugh. I just don't wanna be 30 and still work here.
对  那比到了28岁  还在这里工作更糟糕
Yeah, that'd be much worse than being 28 and still working here.
瑞秋  什么事
Rachel?  Yeah?
提醒我教你分辨  低因咖啡跟一般咖啡
Remind me to review with you which pot is decaf and which is regular.
看把手看不出来吗
Can't I just look at the handles on them?
想得美
You would think.
好吧  阿甘  你知道吗  我是个很差劲的服务生
Okay, fine. Gunther, you know what? I am a terrible waitress.
你知道这是为什么吗   因为我不在乎
Do you know why I'm a terrible waitress? Because I don't care.
我不在乎  我不在乎  低因咖啡跟一般咖啡
I don't care. I don't care which pot is regular and which pot is decaf.
我不在乎托盘区在哪里
I don't care where the tray spot is.
我不在乎  这不是我想做的事
I just don't care. This is not what I wanna do.
我想我不该再做下去了
So I don't think I should do it anymore.
我要跟你提出辞呈  什么
I'm gonna give you my week's notice. What?
阿甘  我不干了
Gunther, I quit.
这表示以后喝咖啡  要付钱了吗
Does this mean we're gonna have to start paying for coffee?
好吧  12
Okay, 12.
Twenty-two.
Eighteen.
什么   我拼出"咪咪"了
What? I spelled out "boobies." Ha, ha.
罗斯  再给我一盒薄荷宝藏  好吗
Ross, put me down for another box of the Mint Treasures, okay?
薄荷宝藏在哪里
Where are the Mint Treasures?
没了  我都卖光了
Uh, we're out. I sold them all.
什么
What?
摩妮卡  我不能再让你吃下去了
Monica, I'm cutting you off.
不行…
No. No.
只是多几盒饼干而已
Just a couple more boxes.
没什么大不了的  我很好
It's no big deal, all right? I'm cool.
你得帮我再拿几盒饼干过来
You gotta help me out with a couple more boxes.
摩妮卡  看看你自己  你的脖子上沾了饼干
Mon, look at yourself. You have cookie on your neck.
天啊
Oh, God.
目前你卖掉几盒了   听好了
Whoa. So how many you sold so far? Ah? Check this out.
517盒  天啊  你怎么办到的
Five hundred and seventeen boxes.  Oh, my God. How did you do that?
好吧   那晚我离开博物馆时
Ahem. Okay, the other night, I was leaving the museum...
雷射弗洛伊德在天文馆演出
...just as Laser Floyd was letting out of the planetarium.
我轻轻松松卖掉五十盒
Without even trying, I sold 50 boxes.
那时我想到这个点子  我的成功之道在于贪嘴
That's when it occurred to me. The key to my success: The munchies.
所以我午夜时跑到纽约大学宿含
So I started hitting the NYU dorms around midnight.
卖掉一箱箱饼干
I am selling cookies by the case.
他们叫我...
They call me...
...饼干兄弟
..."Cookie Dude."
好吧  停下你们手边的工作  我要找人帮忙装信封及贴邮票
Okay, stop what you're doing. I need envelope stuffers, stamp lickers...
谁帮你写履历表的  我用我的电脑写的
Oh, hey. Who did these resumes for you? Me, on my computer.
你还真的用了大号字体
Well, you sure used a large font.
对   "咖啡厅服务生"
Uh, yeah. Well, "Waitress at a Coffeehouse"...
跟"啦啦队长"占不了太多空间
...and "Cheer Squad Co-captain" only took up so much room.
真的好笑
Heh, heh. Hey, that's funny.
你很搞笑  钱德  你是个幽默的家伙
You're funny, Chandler. You're a funny guy.
你知道还有什么事很好笑吗
You know what else is really funny?
我还说了其他的事吗
Something else I might have said?
我不知道
I don't know, I don't know.
不是你要我辞职吗
Weren't you the guy that told me to quit my job...
我根本没有别的事可做
...when I had absolutely nothing else to do?
甜心  冷静点  不会有事的
Sweetie, calm down. It's gonna be okay.
不  会有事的  罗斯
No, it's not gonna be okay, Ross.
明天是最后一天  我一点头绪都没有
Tomorrow is my last day, and I don't have a lead.
好吧  你们知道吗  我要打电话给阿甘
Okay, you know what? I'm just gonna call Gunther...
跟他说我不要辞职
...and I'm gonna tell him I'm not quitting.
你不能屈服在恐惧下
You don't wanna give in to The Fear.
你跟你的愚蠢恐惧  我讨厌你的恐惧
You and your stupid Fear. I hate your Fear.
我要把你和你的恐惧…
I would like to take you and your Fear...
嘿  我有好消息
Hey. I got great news.
逃吧   乔伊   快点逃命
Run, Joey. Run for your life.
什么   瑞秋  听我说  你听说过好运到时装吗
What? Rach, listen, have you ever heard of Fortunata Fashions?
没有   我爸在那里做水电工
No.  My old man's doing a plumbing job there...
听说他们在找人
...and he heard they have an opening.
要我帮你问一下  他能不能帮你争取面试机会吗
Want me to see if he can get you an interview?
天啊  那太棒了  你太好了  乔伊
Oh, my God, yes. I would love that. Oh, that's so sweet, Joey.
别客气  现在才是真正的好消息
Not a problem. And now for the great news.
什么  那不是好消息吗   这个更棒
What, that wasn't the great news? Only if you think it's better than this.
雪花罐
Snow-in-a-Can.
我在工作时拿到的  你要我装饰一下窗户吗
I got it at work. You want me to decorate the window?
做出圣诞造型   圣诞饼干
Give it kind of a Christmas looky? Christmas cookie?
好吧  这棵是道格拉斯杉树
Okay, and this one here's a Douglas fir.
虽然比较贵  但味道很香
Now, it's a little more money, but you get a nicer smell.
看起来不错  我买了
Looks good. I'll take it.
等一下  不  你不会想买那棵
Wait, wait, wait. No, no, no. You don't want that one. Uh-uh.
不  你可以买这棵超酷的枯树
No. You can have this cool brown one. Ooh.
它快死掉了
It's almost dead.
所以你得买下它  它才能完成它的圣诞节使命
But that's why you have to buy it, so that it can fulfill its Christmas destiny.
不然他们会把它丢进碎木机  告诉他  乔伊
Otherwise, they're gonna throw it into the chipper. Tell him, Joey.
啊
Uh...
对  无法完成圣诞节使命的树
Yeah, the trees that don't fulfill their Christmas destiny, heh...
都会被扔进碎木机
...are thrown in the chipper.
我想我要再逛一下
I think I'm gonna look around a little bit more.
菲比  你不能再这么做  我是赚佣金的
Pheebs. Heh. You gotta stop doing this. I'm working on commission here.
两位  我来买圣诞树
Hey, guys. I'm here to pick out my Christmas tree.
别忙了  这是你的圣诞树
Well, look no further. This one's yours.
这是去年我丢掉的吗
Is this the one that I threw out last year?
好吧  你知道吗  算了  大家都想买绿树
All right, you know what? Never mind. Everybody wants to have a green one.
对不起  我也不想这么激动
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to get so emotional.
只是…我想过节让人很伤感
I guess it's just... The holidays are just hard.
甜心  因为你妈妈在圣诞节前后过世的吗
Oh, honey, is that because your mom died around Christmas?
我还没想到那件事呢
Oh, I wasn't even thinking about that.
你好  你卖了几盒
Hi there. How many did you sell?
我不告诉你  你是害莎拉摔断腿的坏人
I'm not gonna tell you. You're the bad man who broke Sarah's leg.
那是个意外  好吗
Hey, now. That was an accident, okay?
你是大坏蛋
You're a big scrud.
那是什么意思
What's a scrud?
你何不去照照镜子  坏蛋
Why don't you look in the mirror, scrud?
我不用照镜子  我看你就行了
I don't have to. I can just look at you.
好了  女孩们
All right, girls...
还有大男人
...and man.
看看你们的最后统计数字
Let's see your final tallies.
黛比
Oh... Debbie.
321盒饼干  非常好
Three hundred and twenty-one boxes of cookies. Very nice.
还不够好
Not nice enough.
夏拉
Charla.
278盒
Two hundred and seventy-eight.
抱歉  亲爱的  还是很不错
Sorry, dear, but still good.
对坏蛋来说够好了
Good for a scrud.
让我看看
Let's see.
是的  伊莉莎白
Ooh. Yes, Elizabeth.
871盒
Eight hundred and seventy-one.
那根本不可能
That's crap.
棕鸟姊妹
Sister Brown Bird.
做得好
Good going.
下一个是谁
Who's next?
你好  你好
Hi there. Hi.
代替莎拉上场
And batting for Sarah...
罗斯盖勒
...Ross Geller.
872盒
Eight hundred and seventy-two.
不过看样子  你自己买了不少饼干
Although it looks like you bought an awful lot of cookies yourself.
因为医生说我有非常严重的
Ahem. That is because my doctor says that I have a very serious...
牛轧糖…
...nougat...
不耐症
...deficiency.
告诉我们发生了什么事  棕鸟罗斯
Tell us what happened, Brown Bird Ross.
我输了
Well, I lost.
有个小女孩把她的制服  借给她19岁的姊姊
Some little girl loaned her uniform to her 19-year-old sister...
她跑到尼米兹号舰艇上  卖掉了两千盒
...who went down to the USS Nimitz and sold over 2000 boxes.
面试怎么样  我搞砸了
Hey. How'd the interview go? Oh, I blew it.
连我自己都不会请我
I wouldn't have even hired me. Oh.
过来  甜心
Ugh. Come here, sweetie.
听着  你得面试一千次  才能找到一份工作
Listen, you're gonna go on like a thousand interviews before you get a job.
我原本不是那个意思
That's not how that was supposed to come out.
这是最糟糕的圣诞节
This is just the worst Christmas ever.
知道吗  瑞秋  或许你该待在咖啡厅工作
Rach, maybe you should just, you know, stay here at the coffeehouse.
不行  太迟了  泰利已经雇用了那个女孩
I can't. It's too late. Terry already hired that girl over there.
看看她  还有当服务生的经验
Look at her. She's even got waitress experience. Ugh.
昨晚她…
Last night she was...
教大家怎么把纸巾折成…
...teaching everybody how to make napkins into...
...天鹅
...swans.
她是说 "天鹅"
That word was "swans."
"天鹅"
"Swans."
看到喝醉酒的圣诞老人尿湿裤子  坏了我的过节兴致
Well, seeing that drunk Santa wet himself really perked up my Christmas.
天啊
Ah! Oh, my God.
圣诞快乐   圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas!
你们救了它们
You saved them. You guys.
天啊  你们最棒了
Oh, God, you're the best.
看起来像是枯死圣诞树复活之夜
Looks like Night of the Living Dead Christmas Trees.
喂
Hello?
对  我就是
Yeah, this is she.
你在开玩笑
Oh! You're kidding. You're kidding.
谢谢  我爱你
Oh, thank you. I love you.
当然  大家都爱开玩笑的人
Sure, everybody loves a kidder.
我被录取了
I got the job.
太棒了  那是最棒的
Oh, hey. All right!  That's great.
上帝保佑所有人
Oh! God bless us, every one.
来吧   这是我最后一次端咖啡
Here we go. I'm serving my last cup of coffee.
来吧  好好享用
There you go. Enjoy.
耶
Yay!
我该跟她说我点的是茶吗   不
Should I tell her I ordered tea?  No.
不   不
No.  No.
对不起  请听我说
Um, excuse me, everyone?
这是我在这里工作的最后一夜
Uh, this is my last night working here...
我只想说我在这里交到一些好朋友
...and I just wanted to say that I made some really good friends here.
是该离开的时候了
And it's just time to move on.
我无意冒犯  留在这里的人
And no offense to everybody who still works here...
但你们不知道我多么开心能这么说
...but you have no idea how good it feels to say...
现在我宣布
...that as of this moment...
我再也不必煮咖啡了
...I will never have to make coffee again.
老卡普兰先生喜欢喝浓咖啡
Now, Mr. Kaplan Sr. Likes his coffee strong.
你得用两包  不是一包
So you're gonna use two bags instead of one, see?
注意听  这个部分很难
Now, pay attention because this part's tricky.
听着  有些人滤纸只用一次
See, some people use filters just once.
抱歉你没办法参加太空营
I'm sorry you didn't get to go to Space Camp...
我希望这能弥补你  好吗
I'm hoping that maybe somehow,this may help make up for it.Okay?
我跟你介绍
Presenting...
莎拉杜铎私人特别太空营
...Sarah Tuddle's Private, Very Special Space Camp!
盖勒先生  你真的不必这么做
Really, Mr. Geller, you don't have to do this.
来吧  要开始了
Oh, come on. Here we go.
准备任务倒数
Stand by for mission countdown.
十…
Ten, ten, ten.
九…
Nine, nine, nine.
八…
Eight, eight, eight. Ow.
好吧  发射
Okay, blast off.
我是外星人
I'm an alien. I'm an alien.
不  是小行星
Oh, no, an asteroid!